https://crochetkim.com/privacy-policy/

Baby Blankets
Cowls Gloves&Mitts Hats Jewelry, Ornaments and Adornments Kitchen and Bath Scarves Shawls
Free Patterns For
Women Holidays Men Baby Girls Boys Instagram Directory
Video Projects Technique
Over 75 Free Tunisian Crochet Patterns Cro-Hook (Double-Ended Tunisian Crochet) Filet Crochet Letter, Number Graphs & Colorwork Charts Slip Stitch Crochet Broomstick Lace Knit Patterns Camel Crochet
Skill Levels
Skill Level: Easy Skill Level: Intermediate Skill Level: Challenging Skill Level: You Can’t Be Serious
Pattern Roundups
Giveaways
CrochetKim™
Menu
Learn
Tunisian Crochet Filet Crochet My Books
Stitch Library
Tunisian Crochet Stitches Lace Crochet Stitches
All Free Patterns
Free Pattern Type
Adult Garment Baby Dresses Bags Blankets
Baby Blankets
Cowls Gloves&Mitts Hats Jewelry, Ornaments and Adornments Kitchen and Bath Scarves Shawls
Free Patterns For
Women Holidays Men Baby Girls Boys Instagram Directory
Video Projects Technique
Over 75 Free Tunisian Crochet Patterns Cro-Hook (Double-Ended Tunisian Crochet) Filet Crochet Letter, Number Graphs & Colorwork Charts Slip Stitch Crochet Broomstick Lace Knit Patterns Camel Crochet
Skill Levels
Skill Level: Easy Skill Level: Intermediate Skill Level: Challenging Skill Level: You Can’t Be Serious
Pattern Roundups
Giveaways
5shares
Share 2
Tweet
Pin 3
CrochetKim.com Privacy Policy Effective Date: 2018-05-24 This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read this privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how your PII is colected, used, protected and otherwise handled. What personal information is collected? When ordering or registering on CrochetKim.com, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience. When is your information collected? Information is collected when you subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on CrochetKim.com. How is your information used? Your information may be used when you register, make a purchase, sign up for an email newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf CrochetKim.com, or use certain other site features in the following ways: • To personalize your experience and to allow CrochetKim.com to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested. • To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. • To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services. How is your information protected? Only articles and information are collected at CrochetKim.com. Your credit card information is never requested. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. A variety of security measures are implemented when someone enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers. Are cookies used at CrochetKim.com? Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, cookies are used at CrochetKim.com to
help measure how you use CrochetKim.com so it can be updated and improved based on your needs remember the notification you’ve seen so that attempts can be made so they’re not shown to you again help compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that better site experiences and tools can be created for the future (third party services may be used to assist in tracking this information for CrochetKim.com) remember you when you making any changes to your email subscription
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. Third-party disclosure CrochetKim.com does not sell, trade or otherwise transfer your PII to outside parties. Third-party links CrochetKim.com offers links to other third party websites that may be of interest to its website visitors. The links provided at CrochetKim.com are provided solely for your convenience and may assist you in locating other useful information on the internet. When you click on these links, you will leave the CrochetKim.com website and will be redirected to another website. These websites are not under the control of CrochetKim.com. CrochetKim.com is not responsible for the content of linked third party websites. CrochetKim.com is not an agent for these third parties nor are the websites endorsed or products guaranteed. No representation is made or warranty regarding the accuracy of the information contained in the linked websites. Always verify the information obtained from linked websites before acting upon this information. Google Analytics This site uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google’s privacy policy is available at: https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links: (a) https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en (Chrome); (b) https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences (Firefox); (c) http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/ (Opera); (d) https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies (Internet Explorer); (e) https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411 (Safari); and (f) https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy (Edge). Please note that blocking cookies may have a negative impact on the functions of many websites, including our Site. Some features of the Site may cease to be available to you. Advertising Privacy Statement This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a CafeMedia (“CafeMedia”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and CafeMedia will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about CafeMedia’s data usage, click here: www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy YouTube videos YouTube is used at CrochetKim.com to provide videos on some pages. YouTube sets cookies when you visit one of these pages. Gleam Gleam is used at CrochetKim.com to run campaigns. Gleam processes this data in accordance with its Privacy Policy which can be read in its entirety at: https://gleam.io/privacy California Online Privacy Protection Act CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following: Visitors can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above. You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes here, on our Privacy Policy Page. You can change your personal information by emailing CrochetKim.com or by logging in to your account. How does CrochetKim.com handle Do Not Track signals? CrochetKim.com honors Do Not Track signals and Does Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. Does CrochetKim.com allow third-party behavioral tracking? Third-party behavioral tracking is allowed. COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act) When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online. CrochetKim.com does not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old. Fair Information Practices The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices CrochetKim.com will notify you by email within one business day should a breach occur. CrochetKim.com also agrees to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors. CAN SPAM Act The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. Your email address is collected to send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. To be in accordance with CANSPAM, CrochetKim.com agrees to: • Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses. • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way. • Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters. • Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used. • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly. • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email to team@crochetkim.com or follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and you will be promptly removed from all correspondence. Sale of Business or Assets In the event that the Site or substantially all of its assets is sold or disposed of as a going concern, whether by merger, sale of assets or otherwise, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, the information we have collected about you may be one of the assets sold or merged in connection with that transaction. Additional Rights of EEA (European Economic Area) Residents If you are a resident of a country in the EEA, you have the rights, among others, to:
access your personal data ensure the accuracy of your personal data the right to have us delete your personal data the right to restrict further processing of your personal data, and the right to complain to a supervisory authority in your country of residence in the event that data is misused.
If you believe that our processing of your personal information infringes data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged infringement. You may exercise any of your rights in relation to your personal data by written notice to us at the address below. Contacting CrochetKim.com If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact using the information below. crochetkim.com 312 W. 2nd St #1151 Casper WY 82601 USA team@crochetkim.com
Many of you have written to me to ask how you can help support CrochetKim. A Patreon account was suggested but I thought it would be better to provide ad-free PDF's of my patterns. You can, of course, view, print ,paste to a word processor, convert to PDF's, etc, on your own. This is just an extra feature so that people help out if they want. Thank you to all of you for your overwhelming support and kindness these many years. Enjoy! View my ad-free patterns here.
Want to help support CrochetKim? View my ad-free patterns here.Stitch Tutorials
© 1998-2020. All rights reserved. CrochetKim™ Property owned by Three Needles LLC.
Disclaimer:  As an Amazon Associate I earn from qualifying purchases.
